

RASHIDHA KATHOON KS

UX/UI & CREATIVE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACTS

- +91 996 297 7923
- rashidhakathoon 3@gmail.com
- Chennai

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Photoshop	
Illustrator	
InDesign	
Figma	
Coreldraw	
PowerPoint	
MS Word	
Excel	

LANGUAGES KNOWN

Tamil English

EXPERIENCE

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm a UX/UI & Creative Graphic Designer, with hands on experience of 6.6 years in Digital & Print Media. Am Good in UX Research, UI Designs and also i have experience in Product ads, website Banners, Logos, Brochures, Flyers, Product Packaging & Labeling Designs

WORK EXPERIENCE

- UX/UI & Visual Designer
 HCL Technologies
 Since OCT 2021
- UI & Creative Graphic Designer
 Shree Varma Bio Naturals Pvt. Ltd.
 FEB 2019 to OCT 2021
- Imaging Associate (Color Author)
 Amazon
 AUG 2017 to NOV 2017

Imaging Associate

Lumina Datamatics
 Jan 2016 to May 2017

EDUCATION

St. Joseph's College Of Arts & Science, Chennai
 BSC Visual Communication (91%) 2013 - 2016

PORTFOLIO LINK

https://www.behance.net/rashidhakathoon